♪From primal chaos to the starry sky♪
♪In the whole world,
we shall hold the balance♪
♪The cauldron tempers divine blades♪
♪The furnace refines the empty void♪
♪The Way is in mystic fate♪
♪Be brave enough to split
the primal chaos wide open♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel
by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
I'm Youqin Xuanya of Ascendance Sect.
Please instruct me, seniors.
Of all in the outer hall
not in the Register,
only this one remains.
It must be the Inner Treasury entrance.
No.
Since there are guards,
there must be
a mechanism restriction too.
To be safe, I'll come back next time.
You're from Ascendance Sect,
yet you don't use magic?
I have my reasons.
Please forgive us, seniors.
How annoying.
She's still respecting us now.
It's just a few immortal treasures.
Let's just go easy on her.
We can go easy on her,
but will His Highness do the same to us?
We'll only use 20% of our power.
It all depends on your luck.
[Episode 8]
Xuanya.
Elder Kuai.
It's already this intense.
Aren't you going to help her?
Yes, go help her, quick.
Your Highness,
Kuai Si is too humiliated to hold on.
You have a point.
Don't say it so loud.
What a hassle.
- How? - Beautiful!
- Xuanya is amazing!
- Senior is formidable!
Call a few people.
Let them beat that girl out!
That's not what you said earlier!
Your Highness, His Majesty has ordered.
Even if we are
to humiliate the Human Clan,
it must be done by proper means.
We can't give them
any excuse for trouble.
Someone helped me!
Why are you hitting me?
Then why are you hitting me?
Move!
Xuanya.
Are you all right?
- Great!
- No worries.
Awesome!
Senior, I...
I've got them all.
First Prince,
in that case...
Very impressive.
Does that count as my win?
You are hard to finish off.
You pass.
As for what's inside,
pick anything you like.
Your Highness.
What is happening?
She...
She comes with ill intent.
This Resonance...
What?
It's her.
Stop pulling. It hurts!
Stop pulling me.
Who goes there?
You are in East Sea. Show yourself.
Or we shall draw you out.
A fine offering.
Ugly indeed.
This...
Ascendance Sect disciples, heed me.
This is the Dragon Palace's business.
Everyone, fall back.
Back!
Ow! Ow!
What are you doing?
All units, send two more teams!
Primordial...
Primordial Vessel!
Could she be Fairy Yunxiao
of Jadecourt Palace, Trifairy Isle,
disciple of Heavenreach Master,
foremost of the Seizing Sect?
Fairy Yunxiao.
You know her?
A little.
Fairy,
I failed to recognize your greatness.
Forgive my lack of proper welcome.
Here, I offer...
Let the East Sea master speak with me.
Sure.
Dear Fairy.
You've come at last!
His Majesty is here!
- His Majesty!
- Fairy!
You've come at last!
This is the Dragon King?
Why does he look so sleazy?
You can tell at a glance
that he's a lecherous dragon.
The Trifairy Isle is near the sea.
We've been good neighbors for years.
Fairy, what took you so long?
I've been waiting for you!
I came uninvited.
I hope I didn't disturb your rest.
This...
You're too kind.
A celestial being graces us.
Our humble home shines bright.
Might I inquire what matter
brings you all this way?
I know the Dragon Palace
is rich in treasures,
so I'm here
to borrow a treasure from you.
Of course!
We've been neighbors for years.
Take whatever you wish.
Attendant!
Escort the Fairy to Lotus Hall.
Let her choose freely.
But the treasure I need
may not be there.
What treasure do you have in mind?
The Sea-Calming Pillar.
The Sea-Calming Pillar?
What?
How dare you!
The Sea-Calming Pillar is
our greatest treasure.
You can't just demand to borrow it.
Jia.
Why get so worked up?
Since you've spoken,
you must be determined to have it.
But as they say,
skilled riders fall;
good swimmers drown.
Fairy,
please think carefully.
I've always been reckless.
I love to charge against the waves.
Tomorrow,
I'll give it to you as you wish.
But please grant me one more night.
The treasure's movement
requires fasting,
purification, and rites.
Tomorrow morning,
I'll present the treasure. How's that?
Block me.
Hi, hi.
You know each other?
I heard that lately,
Fairy Yunxiao
started asking
about the Sea-Calming Pillar.
Ten from Ascendance Sect,
one Dragon Clan General.
So, the total should be...
Eleven.
It should be eleven people,
but there are twelve spiritual senses.
Come in.
Senior.
Here to get gifts?
So many?
One means a thousand times.
Never mind a thousand times.
Ten thousand times is worth it.
There are so many treasures here.
How is Junior Xuanya?
She's fine. She's already lain down.
Senior,
was it you who saved
Senior Xuanya inside today?
Yes.
I knew it!
Why did you insist on Lotus Hall today?
It must be for her, right?
Wrong answer. Add two thousand more.
I just knew it.
How could you be thinking
of someone else?
It must be me!
Wrong answer.
Add another two thousand.
Then what is it really for?
Fairy Yunxiao at the hall today...
What about her?
She went to borrow
the Sea-Calming Pillar.
But she said she knew the Pillar
wasn't in the Lotus Hall.
How did she know that?
Since she knew
the Pillar was not in Lotus Hall,
why did she storm Lotus Hall then?
Senior,
she's an immortal of the Seizing Sect.
Her cultivation
surpasses our Grandlord's.
Why should I care about that?
A divine lamp.
I'm not after some treasure.
I'm after a person.
No.
She wasn't there for the Pillar.
Then what was she there for?
She came to let me know she's here.
She wants to see me.
Here.
Be gentle.
Sure.
Time to look inside.
Whose turn is it?
I just went. Now, it's your turn.
I just went. It's your turn.
Nonsense. Who went just now?
I did.
Go.
You forgot. It must be you who forgot.
Quick, quick. You go.
You go.
From your first day here,
you've been slacking off.
- Will you go or not?
- Hurry up.
What are you looking at?
Who are you?
Two handsome gentlemen, I'm...
a lobster.
I'm here for lost
and found.
Take a look. Take a look.
Does this belong to either of you?
[Beauty Portrait]
Stop shaking it.
Is it? Is it?
[Beauty Portrait]
No, no!
We're not that kind of men.
Take it away.
No, no!
I have another one here.
A true treasure. A treasure!
How is it?
Here I come.
Indeed.
Leaving in such a hurry?
Put me down!
A thief!
Well, well.
Miss, I'm afraid of heights!
Please put me down.
Miss.
This treasure is quite intriguing.
Little girl,
who sent you?
Well...
Miss, you've misunderstood.
I'm just lost, you see.
Which way to the latrine?
I'll take you there.
Miss,
put me down first, okay?
Put me down, and we'll talk.
In your dreams.
Who's this thief stealing treasure?
Oh, it's the Fairy.
Thank you for your trouble, Fairy.
If not for you, Fairy,
this thief would have slipped through.
It was nothing.
Fairy, you must be startled.
I can handle this.
I have eighty ways to kill her.
Let me.
I will stay here tonight.
Then...
Fairy, make yourself at home.
How cruel of you.
A true heir of Ascendance Sect.
Flowing wind, moistening water.
Silence.
For you, chant-bound spells
show far too little cultivation.
Your cultivation is far beyond this.
Fairy, you know me?
Kuru Land.
Thanks for securing Skyscraping Vine.
Not at all.
Fairy, you like plants too?
Skyscraping Vine can reach the heavens.
But the place I must go
is beyond even Skyscraping Vine.
You're a mere Human Clan disciple.
Why do you need Skyscraping Vine?
Here's the thing.
My place was just redone.
I need a few to clear the smell.
You like crafts too?
These scouts are handy indeed.
You put much thought into them.
I came to the East Sea to scout it.
But then I found
many paper butterflies already set.
That person must know the East Sea
like the back of their hand.
That impressive?
Why not ask him, Fairy?
I know not who set them.
But I do know
that if I show myself,
they will come to me,
for we seek the same thing.
So, you stirred things up
at Lotus Hall?
I chose Lotus Hall
because everyone was there,
including you.
The moment I saw you, I knew
the paper butterflies must be your work.
How could you be certain?
In Kuru Land,
I've already seen your methods.
So,
you're here to interrogate me
for the Sea-Calming Pillar?
If you're willing to tell me,
we could save a lot of time.
If you want to know,
I'll certainly tell you.
Actually, this Sea-Calming Pillar...
It...
Now!
Fairy, take care.
Thank you, Fairy.
A mere mechanism restriction.
You used me to open the door on purpose.
Things are tough now.
I have to go with the flow.
According to the map,
that thing should be nearby.
[By Grand Mage,
Sea-Calming Pillar Diagram]
Here it is.
Well done.
You used me to avoid the traps.
I used you to steal the item.
We're even.
What a surprise.
I thought I had it all planned.
Yet your power trumps all.
Still not steady enough.
Wrong.
You lose
precisely because you were too steady.
Have you ever made a mistake?
No.
Have you ever dared to defy the world,
bathe in blood, and risk it all?
I...
You certainly haven't.
You're the kind I hate most.
You always keep a way out for yourself,
playing it safe.
When it matters most,
righteousness, rules,
and even your comrades
can be cast aside.
Right?
I...
Giving it one's all
is the greatest joy.
You've never experienced it,
so you won't understand my feelings.
Fairy, Fairy.
I'll confess everything.
Actually,
Junior and I have always been
in love.
Our private diary is in the treasury.
[Yuan Qing, I miss you. Senior Kuai Si]
[Junior Yuan Qing]
Her name is Yuan Qing?
And you are Kuai Si?
Yes. I am Kuai Si.
I swear it here.
If I lie, may I die wretchedly.
[Kuai Si, love is now memory. Yuan Qing]
You went to great trouble.
Even the forgery looks flawless.
However,
my patience is gone.
If you will not hand it over,
I shall take it myself.
The Sea-Calming Pillar
is truly here.
Did the Dragon King promise
to give the Pillar to you?
Had I believed him,
why wait for you in Lotus Hall?
If this map is real,
to find the Sea-Calming Pillar,
I must first locate the Eye of the Sea.
So, where is the Eye of the Sea?
How would I know?
You've surveyed the East Sea's terrain.
How could you not know where it is?
Then...
What if I'm just stupid?
What will it take for you to tell me?
Fairy, answer me a question first.
Go on.
Fairy, well...
You followed us into the Dragon Palace
and only revealed yourself today.
There's only one explanation.
You have someone inside, right?
You guessed right.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Then how did you contact them?
Why did they send you here?
And why should I tell you?
Okay.
To show my sincerity,
I'll trade three secrets
of the Sea-Calming Pillar
with you.
Go on.
Then I'll get up and tell you.
The first secret:
Though the Pillar's name
contains the word "Pillar",
actually, it's...
Someone's in the way.
But it's not a pillar.
Then what is it?
It's a kind
of rod that holds up the sky.
It links the heaven and sea.
Though it can take the shape of a stick
and an embroidery needle,
yet it weighs 13,500 jin.
Even all the guards of the Dragon Palace
cannot budge it one bit.
The Pillar hasn't been seen in ages.
You've seen it?
In a way, I have.
Now, the second secret...
I'm telling you this for your own good.
The Pillar bears immense karma.
It's not yours to bear.
You couldn't endure it.
How would you know that?
The one who takes the Pillar
will become an enemy
of the Celestial Realm,
undergo the furnace refinement
for 49 days,
and be pinned
under a mountain for 500 years.
Can you bear that karma?
I'll know
once I try.
Fairy, don't be hasty.
There's a third secret.
There is a way
to avoid the karma
and still claim the Pillar.
Tell me.
Wait another thousand years.
A thousand years later,
a great immortal will pass by here
and take the Pillar.
He will defy the Celestial Realm
and battle the celestial soldiers.
Then, he'll be trapped
under a mountain for 500 years.
When he's trapped,
you go find him
and snatch the Pillar.
Wouldn't that be perfect?
How did the great immortal
get the Pillar?
He'll shrink it to fit inside his ear.
Who is he?
He's not a human.
He's a monkey.
Where did he come from?
He burst forth from a stone.
You've got to be kidding me.
When...
You're stalling for time.
Fairy,
this blaze will draw
the Dragon Palace army here soon.
If you don't flee now,
you may never get the chance.
To save your life,
you went to great lengths
with this scheme.
Trouble at Lotus Hall! Follow me!
Move!
What's going on?
Frog!
Eel!
Wake up!
Hurry.
Fire!
Go.
Do you really think this could trap me?
I underestimated you,
but
you underestimated me, too.
Since I chose this path,
even if I'm reduced to ashes,
I will never retreat.
I...
Go put out the fire!
It's you again, Yunxiao!
We treated you with courtesy,
yet you set the house on fire!
- After her!
- Hurry!
You saved us?
You broke into Lotus Hall at night.
If the Dragon Palace learned,
it'd be dangerous, right?
Why?
You told me three secrets.
Let me share one in return.
Someone lured me to the East Sea,
but I don't know who they were
or what they looked like.
Is that true?
Who knows?
Perhaps I'm lying to you too.
If it is true,
it must be a trap.
I know.
But I have no choice.
Little brat,
you and I are both at fate's mercy.
Take care of yourself.
Speak freely if you
have something to say.
Fairy, why burn Lotus Hall?
Must you meddle in all my affairs?
Fairy,
you don't want to say?
Don't you claim to hear everything
and know everything?
Someone cast a spell,
blocking my ears and eyes.
So,
your cultivation is lacking.
What's that to me?
Fairy, why go to Lotus Hall?
Who was the person who spoke
with you there?
That's none of your concern.
Fairy, don't forget:
I brought you to the East Sea.
Without my help,
you'd be unable to move an inch.
Unable to move an inch?
Why don't you try?
I helped you come to the East Sea.
If you're hiding something,
how can I offer all my help?
Fairy, don't forget
the Fated Mandate you bear.
I'll go check the Sea-Calming Pillar.
Did you find it?
It's in the East Sea's forbidden zone.
Fairy, you truly are amazing.
I'm willing to guide you, Fairy.
Who exactly are you?
What are you plotting
in helping me?
Fairy, why ask so many questions?
Even if it's a plot,
you'll still go.
Because, Fairy,
you have no choice.
The words are said; the way is shown.
You can choose
to believe it or not, Fairy.
♪Birds in the trees fly in pairs♪
I'll wrap more for you.
That way you can't break up.
Where is your true love?
Let me look for your true love.
[Li Changshou]
Why is there an extra red thread?
Where does this one connect to?
Ah, Li Changshou.
I wondered why you were
as stubborn as a rock.
So, there's a new development.
I've got to see
where this red thread leads.
Who's this?
Moon Elder.
Changshou?
You're here to catch up
on sleep in your dreams?
I've achieved a great feat.
Please let me talk to your supervisor.
You...
You must be dreaming.
How great?
I'm not dreaming. That's a great feat.
What did you say?
Fairy Yunxiao went to the East Sea.
Who are you?
Where did you come from?
A job seeker. He's called Changshou.
I don't care about his name.
Why did you bring him to me?
Fairy Yunxiao's intrusion
into the Dragon Palace
was for the Sea-Calming Pillar.
How do you know about the Pillar?
How do you know?
This...
When Fairy Yunxiao was at the East Sea,
she told me herself.
She told you herself?
In that case,
Fairy Yunxiao has already begun.
Ah, yes.
Upon hearing this,
he swooshed up to the Celestial Court.
That's a great feat indeed.
Please send
the celestial soldiers at once.
We must not let Fairy Yunxiao succeed.
What do you know?
You know how far it is to the East Sea?
Even if I send
the celestial soldiers now,
it will take time.
It takes time, you know.
My true body is in the East Sea.
I'll serve the Celestial Court.
You want to aid the Celestial Court?
Look at yourself.
Who are you? Where did you come from?
Aren't you bragging a bit too much?
I bet there's not a single bull left
in all the realms.
You just bragged them all to death.
I've clashed with Fairy Yunxiao once.
Fairy Yunxiao is indeed powerful
and clever.
But I still believe
I can stop this crisis
and protect the Pillar.
I can end the human-dragon feud
and secure land for Celestial Court.
Young man, those words...
How should I describe this lad?
This...
How reliable.
Fine. I think I understand.
But I have to ask...
You...
Where does your confidence come from?
I need only clarify one matter.
Then I will have a plan.
Reliable.
Senior.
Senior, you're finally awake.
You've been out for ten years.
Ten years?
Then let me see your copies
of the Scripture of Steadiness
during these ten years.
So boring. You can't even pretend.
Still cracking jokes.
So, you're not too hurt.
Not hurt?
I'm not just not hurt.
I'm bouncing with energy.
Did Ms. Yunxiao casually heal me?
Would she be that kind?
I don't think she's a bad person.
Yes, she doesn't seem like a bad person.
She's simply not human.
A Quasi-Saint, rare in this world.
How do you know her name?
When you were unconscious just now,
you kept murmuring her name.
Yunxiao, Yunxiao, Fairy...
I was talking about Yunxiao...
No, sweet dumplings.
Yes.
No, not important.
We have more important things to do.
What important things?
Since these humans came here,
there's trouble every day.
They must be behind it.
Don't let me catch them.
Or else...
How bold to steal treasures again!
What do you want?
That's my line!
The keys are in your hands.
You even want to accuse us first?
I have the keys; I can come and go.
You admit it!
You've confessed without being pressed.
Confess?
Confess what?
Surprise!
A traitor in the Dragon Palace!
Traitor?
I'm no traitor!
But Senior, if we say he's a traitor,
will the First Prince believe us?
Stop talking nonsense.
Right, that's right.
That's right.
Mere talk won't do, of course.
But we caught him red-handed.
I have the keys; I can come and go.
Give it to me!
You think I won't kill you?
You'd kill us?
If you dare kill me,
I'll take that
and tell the First Prince.
Do you believe me?
Come on, kill me.
Come on.
Come on, kill me, then.
You two...
General,
we look
so upright and kind.
Why would we harm you on purpose?
We truly mean well.
We just need a small favor.
If you still refuse,
then we
must ruin your future.
You two...
Can we talk this over?
Si'er,
I searched East Palace for you.
Why come to West Palace alone?
Your Highness, why come here
instead of sleeping?
I'm bored.
I was too harsh yesterday.
So, I came to check
whether you were hurt.
You waited a day to check?
I've been busy.
Father put the humans in my charge.
And Fairy Yunxiao showed up
and burned my Lotus Hall.
I was afraid you'd run into her
and get hurt again.
Thank you for your concern,
Your Highness.
I am the Princess of the Mermaid Clan.
If I really run into her,
I won't be so easily harmed.
Okay.
It seems
I worried too much.
I was just being presumptuous.
Your Highness.
You care about me.
I won't be ungrateful.
I just wish
you'd be the old you again.
You used to be so...
What was I like before?
Why bring this up again?
What of the past, and what of now?
I am who I am.
Ridiculous.
Your Highness.
Hurry up.
Your Highness! This is urgent!
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Crown Prince.
This is urgent.
You brought them here?
Turn around.
Not again.
You want to be kicked straight on?
Who let you bring humans here?
I can't stand the human smell.
Crown Prince,
study his rear in your chamber.
The Dragon Palace is in trouble!
Yes, yes, really in trouble.
Audacious! You're the one in trouble.
Really, really.
Your Highness, there really is trouble.
This human cultivator
excels at divination.
We'd better believe it's false.
What?
Believe what?
Better to believe it's true.
Right, don't believe it's true.
What nonsense!
I...
Your Highness, I have a plan.
It can save the East Sea
and make you a great hero.
But this plan
needs this little disciple.
You
have a plan?
He has a plan.
Really?
[Void Forbidden Land]
[Forbidden]
The Sea-Calming Pillar is indeed here.
This little rascal
finally told the truth.
The Primordial Vessel can't budge it.
Could it be
that it really has the karma he said?
What's this?
Fairy, please show mercy!
Fairy.
I was wrong to deceive you, Fairy.
But, Fairy,
you burned my Lotus Hall
and destroyed thousands of my treasures.
That should've made up for it.
How about this?
Let's both compromise.
Let's wipe the slate clean.
How does that sound?
Then how about this?
We both take a step forward.
Lend me the Sea-Calming Pillar.
Once I finish my task,
I'll come to be bound and punished.
How's that?
Okay.
So, you agree?
But it's a pity.
Good as it is,
it's not feasible.
The Eye of the Sea is thick with miasma.
Only the Pillar can quell it.
So, you refuse.
Aside from the Primordial Vessel,
you've also got
Cloudlink Hermit's Fiendscour Mirror,
Crimson Spirit's Tideflame Edge,
and Virtue Lord's Soulgore Nail.
I have heard that lately,
you've changed, making enemies.
Even your Seizing Sect fellows
are baffled.
So, the rumors are true after all.
Beneath this Eye of the Sea,
what dire beast is sealed below?
What dire beast?
Did you not hear
that cry just now?
I heard nothing.
The realms of the fleeting world
are filled with mad pretenders.
Pregenesis Sword.
What did you say?
Back then, the Grand Mage of Voidcity
set down this Sea-Calming Pillar
to seal the East Sea's Eye.
The Grand Mage's power
surpasses yours.
So, you can't break this seal
or take the Sea-Calming Pillar.
But the Pregenesis Sword can?
That's right.
The Pregenesis Sword
is the only magic instrument
to break the seal.
♪See mortal joys and sorrows♪
♪Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds♪
♪Alas, love has many twists and turns♪
♪Memories filled with sorrow♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tearfully,
this life's bond is not over♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪
♪Down a few more cups of wine♪
♪Through land and sea,
I ask you to come♪
♪For honor's sake, upright and grand♪
♪Alas, our story is short♪
♪Slowly, wishes turn to regret♪
♪You've gone afar, like mist fading♪
♪Tears fall, this fate's not done♪
♪Past fragments vanish into night♪